dailyviralupdates.com 2017-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Daily Viral Updates

Your privacy is very important to us at DailyViralUpdates, and so we have a few fundamental principles that we follow in order to protect it:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures DailyViralUpdates (“we”, “our” or “us”) uses regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any information that you give us when you use www.dailyviralupdates.com (the “Website”) and the services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively with the Website, the “Services”). We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. When we ask you to provide certain information when using the Website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. By using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy.

We may change this policy from time to time by posting changes to this page. You can occasionally check to make sure that you are happy with any changes.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter (from which you can unsubscribe at any time), respond to a survey or fill out a form. You may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may always, however, visit our site anonymously.

**Your Information Is Protected:  **

We are committed to ensuring that your personal information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place a variety of physical, electronic and managerial security measures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.dailyviralupdates.com does not use cookies.

**Third Party Vendors:**

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads to you based on a your prior web site visits to DailyViralUpdates and/or other websites. You may opt out of the use of the Google cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

**Links To Third Party Websites:**

We may sometimes include on our website links to other websites that may be of interest to you. You should note that these third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies, and that we do not have any control over those other websites. Therefore, we have no responsibility or liability for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites, or for the content and activities of those sites. You should exercise caution and review the privacy policies applicable to the website in question.

Advertisement
